Nitin Sir, the ICICI
Insurance company had a
breakout in June,
around 1185, and this 1150 was very good.
This breakout zone is becoming its support.
1215 is currently trading. 1185 is
also looking very strong ahead. After
falling below 1215, the level of 1185 is visible,
but I don't think that 1185 will be able to
withstand this time and will
not get support because the final
support that is being formed is around 1155. So, I
feel that somewhere major, the
stock can fall till 1150-55, it is on the
downside where you
can enter. In the first left, I would say that
you can invest 40% of the money here
around 1150, because after this, the final level that is being formed is
around 1000-80. The
remaining 40% can
also be invested by you at 1150. After investing at these two levels,
you can hold it for one year.  Forget it,
this stock's minimum level of 1400 plus would have
ended in 2023, so if we
talk about 2024, then
I think by the end of 2024,
this stock will probably reach 1700 plus.
But the support levels you are mentioning,
Nitin Sir, if
my entry is already near those levels, then should I
book profit here at once,
around 1185, where support is being formed.
From 1185, you have only 100 points
more to fall because the second level I
mentioned, the final level, is around 100080.
Now, if you can see 100 points, then
I would say do not book profit because
in the coming time, all these stocks are going to move very
fast. The levels I have
mentioned are 1400 plus in one year or
1700 plus in two years, so it is very good, the
rewards are going to be received within this, so gather the
points, if you can see them, then you should see them,
if you cannot see them, you feel that there is a
lot of turmoil.  It will happen if you
are a patient of high blood pressure then I will tell you to
come out, otherwise you can stay inside it, it
also happens that if it does not affect you then
you can stay in it,
some people think that once you
book a profit here, you are already making a profit of ₹100, it will happen right now
from your level or whatever it is and after that
your capital will have increased, then when you go to
enter again, you will take ₹100 more and you will be
able to buy some extra shares, so people think in that way also,
everyone thinks according to their own way, in the way that suits you,
whenever you enter any stock, now give it
15 minutes, why are you entering it for that stock, for
what target are you
entering it and for what time are you entering it
and you enter the reason for deciding this, then it is important for the
decision,
like if I tell you that I have bought sugar stock
for 2025, no matter what happens to me, I will
not exit, I will invest
in some stock by 2025  When I enter,
I see that I want 10% profit in it. The
day I get 10%, the
day the
stock rises by 50% after the balance,
but since my decision is that I
want 10%, I exit at 10%.
Because if you do it with this calculation,
you get a satisfaction. So,
in whichever stock you enter, you should have
two things clear about your profit and time frame. We
cannot enter anywhere openly that we will get it entered.
You should
definitely leave the stock when your target is good.